RESUME

Sachin Modhera

Medical Biller, Accountant, Business Processing Outcast Agent (BPO)

SUMMARY

PROFILE

Name

Sachin Pravinbhai Modhera

Date of Birth

7, August 2001

Address

Nr Anand Ashram, Sarkhej-Dholka Road, Ahmadabad, 382210

Phone

9724255117

Email

SachinModhera07@gmail.com

Business Processing Outcast Agent (BPO). Passionate customer service representative with one year of experience. Willing to work in Accounts Management.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2017 2018 - 2019	V. V. Patel Vidhya Mandir, passed by SSC with 85 %.
	Passed HSC from V. V. Patel Vidhya Mandir with 75 %.
2019- 2021	Completed B. Com at R. J. Tibrewal Commerce College with 52 %.

JOB EXPERIENCES

March 2020 to may 2021 Paras Consultant, as a medical biller.

Jun 2021 to aug Business Processing Outcast Agent at T-Tec.

October 2022 to 2023 AMD INTEGRAL As An Accountant

SKILLS / HOBBIES

- Microsoft Office
- Medical Billing
- Cricket
- Excel and Tally

basic

knowledge of

QuickBooks